buzzify.co.uk 2016-01-13

# Privacy Policy - Buzzify

This Privacy Policy has been prepared to meet the requirements of the Data Protection Act 1998, and it only relates to the collection, protection, disclosure and use of personal data belonging to living individuals. It does not relate to data, which emanates from companies or other entities. Buzzify is registered with the Information Commissioner’s Office (“ICO”) under the Act with registration number ZA007309 and will act as the data controller.

This Policy (together with our Terms & Conditions and Cookie Policy and any other documents referred to in it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data.

### 1\. INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU

1.1 We may collect and process the following data about you:

1.1.1 information that you may provide by filling in online forms and registration forms on this website (the “Site”), and we may also ask you for information in the event you report a problem with our Site;

1.1.2 correspondence, or a record of it should you contact us;

1.1.3 surveys that we use for research purposes, which we may ask you to complete, although you do not have to respond to them;

1.1.4 details of your visits to our Site (including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise) and the resources that you access;

1.1.5 information to help verify your identity;

1.1.6 information from third parties in respect of you, which may include your employer, a referee or a person residing or working from another country.

### 2\. IP ADDRESSES AND COOKIES

Please also refer to the Cookie Policy.

2.1 A “cookie” is a small electronic file that collects information when someone visits a website. A cookie can identify the pages that are being viewed, and this can assist us to select the pages that the viewer sees. Some cookies only exist whilst viewers are online, but “persistent” cookies – which are not session-based – remain on the viewer’s computer, so that he or she can be recognised as a previous visitor when he or she next visits our Site. This allows us to collect information about a viewer’s browsing habits whilst on our Site, and this can be useful in assisting us to monitor and improve our services.

2.2 We do not store sensitive information such as account numbers or passwords in “persistent” cookies, and cookies in themselves, do not contain enough information to identify you. You will only acquire a personal identity in relation to your browsing habits after you have formally provided us with your personal data for the purposes outlined below.

2.3 In addition to using cookies, we might also use web tools to collect information about your browsing activities whilst on our Site. In this respect the information that is provided is similar to the information supplied by cookies, and we use it for the same purposes.

2.4 Any information that we acquire about you using cookies or web tools is subject to the same restrictions and conditions as any other information we collect about you.

2.5 Some of our advertisers may also use cookies or web tools that are set by other people such as advertising agencies, or the businesses to which the advertisements in question relate. We do not have access to any information that might be collected in this way, and, if you are concerned, you should contact the advertiser for more information.

2.6 If you want to delete any cookies already stored on your computer or stop the cookies that keep track of your browsing patterns on the Site, you can do so by deleting your existing cookies and/or altering your browser’s privacy settings to block third party cookies (the process you follow will differ from browser to browser). Please note that deleting our cookies or disabling our future cookies means that you may not be able to access certain areas or features of the Site

### 3\. WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA

3.1 Buzzify employs industry standard security measures to ensure the security of all data. Any data that is stored on Buzzify secure servers is treated as proprietary and confidential and is not available to the public. Buzzify has an internal security policy with respect to the confidentiality of customer and other data, allowing access only to those employees or third parties who have a need to know such information for the purpose of effectively delivering Buzzify products and services by means of user login and password requirements. Buzzify routinely evaluates its data security practices to identify security threats or opportunities for improvement.

3.2 No transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under the control of Buzzify to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect your data, Buzzify cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.

3.3 We ask you not to permit anyone to use your name. We will retain your information securely stored for a reasonable period or for as long as the law requires.

### 4\. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

4.1 We use information held about you in the following ways:

4.1.1 to process and submit your application form to credit intermediaries or lenders (“Our Partners”);

4.1.2 to pass to our third party marketing partners (if you have provided your consent for us to do so);

4.1.3 to provide you with the best possible service;

4.1.4 to ensure that content from our Sites is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;

4.1.5 to notify you about changes to our products and services; and

4.1.6 for research purposes.

4.2 We use your data to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you, and we may contact you about these by post, e-mail, telephone and/or text message. We may receive information from another lead provider/broker, namely any third party entity which provides services or information to customers regarding the availability and terms for business finance and which provides us with information and customer lead generation.

4.3 If you wish to opt-out of receipt of these marketing communications from us at any time you may do so by sending an email by clicking here or by writing to us Buzzify 5B Steam Mill Business Centre, Steam Mill Street, Chester, CH3 5AN

4.4 If you opt-out of our use of your data for marketing purposes, we will honour such choice once we have had a reasonable opportunity to process your request. We reserve the right to take reasonable steps to authenticate your identity with respect to any such request or other enquiry.

4.5 If you have provided us with consent to pass your details onto third parties, then third parties may use your data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you, and they may contact you about these by post, e-mail, telephone and/or text message. If you wish to opt-out of continuing to receive such marketing communications, you should contact the third party directly.

4.6 Any information or statistics relating to our business that we disclose to others shall not identify you personally. We may, for example, perform statistical analysis of the behaviour of the users of our Site in order to measure interest in the various areas of our Site and to inform advertisers as to how many consumers have seen or clicked their advertising banners. This information, and any other general information about our users that we share with advertisers and other partners, will not disclose personal information about you.

### 5\. DATA TRANSFER

5.1 Personal data held shall only be transferred to a country outside the EEA if there is adequate protection in that country.

5.2 It is sometimes necessary for Buzzify to transfer personal data to the US for processing purposes. Such data transfer has been notified to the ICO in compliance with the Act.

### 6\. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

6.1 We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

6.1.1 to prepare or send any communications to you, or to assist us in connection with any of our administrative or business functions, or in the provision of any of our services to you;

6.1.2 if Buzzify or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party personal data held by us about our customers will be one of the transferred assets;

6.1.3 if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms & Conditions and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Buzzify, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

6.2 We may give information about you and how you manage your account to the following:

6.2.1 people who provide a service to us or are acting as our agents on the understanding that they will keep the information confidential. If they are located in another country we will make sure that they agree to apply the same levels of protection as we are required to apply to information held in the UK, and to use your information only for the purpose of providing the service to us;

6.2.2 to anyone to whom we transfer or may transfer our rights and duties under this agreement; and

6.2.3 we may also give out information about you if we have a duty to do so or if the law allows us to do so.

6.3 Otherwise, we will keep information about you confidential.

### 7\. INFORMATION SHARING

7.1 Buzzify may make any data provided in response to an advertisement available to the company sponsoring the advertisement, as well as to other trusted third parties in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy. As a result, you may receive information on additional products, services and offers that may be of interest to you.

7.2 Buzzify and/or our marketing partners may enhance and/or merge data about consumers who have opted-in to receive marketing communications with commercially-available third party data collected from other sources in an effort to ensure that the messages being sent to the consumer in online and/or offline marketing programs are relevant to their interests. We will take reasonable steps to maintain the integrity and quality of that information that we enhance and/or merge with data collected from other sources.

7.3 Buzzify may share data (including information that has been enhanced with information from other sources) with advertisers, third party marketers and our affiliated entities for their online and/or offline marketing programs. While Buzzify strongly encourages clients and partners to adopt responsible approaches to online marketing, Buzzify is not responsible for the information practices of clients or their partners. The collection, use, and disclosure of information by clients and partners are subject to their respective privacy policies, which may differ from Buzzify.

### 8\. YOUR RIGHTS

8.1 Our Site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

8.2 Section 7 of the Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act by writing to us at Buzzify 5B Steam Mill Business Centre, Steam Mill Street, Chester, CH3 5AN. Any access request may be subject to a small statutory fee to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

8.3 If you were introduced to us by a third party, we will give them your contact details and sufficient information about you for their accounting and administration purposes.

8.4 Buzzify will attempt to resolve any complaint that you may have in relation to data protection issues. In the alternative, or if you are not happy with our final response you have the right to have your complaint dealt with by the ICO.

### 9\. CREDIT REFERENCE AND FRAUD PREVENTION AGENCIES

9.1 When you submit an application form you confirm that all the information you have given is true and complete. When you submit an application form you authorise Our Partners to check the following records about you and others:

9.1.1 our own;

9.1.2 those at credit reference agencies (“CRAs”); and

9.1.3 those at fraud prevention agencies (“FPAs”).

9.2 Our Partners will make checks such as are deemed necessary to assess your application for credit.

9.3 If you tell us that you have a spouse or financial associate, Our Partners will link your records together so you must be sure that you have their agreement to disclose information about them. CRAs also link your records together and these links will remain on your and their files until such time as you or your partner successfully files for a disassociation with the CRAs to break that link.

9.4 If false or inaccurate information is provided and fraud is identified, details will be passed to fraud prevention agencies.

9.5 Law enforcement agencies may access and use this information.

9.6 We and other organisations including Our Partners may also access and use this information to prevent fraud and money laundering, for example, when:

9.6.1 checking details on applications for credit and credit related or other facilities;

9.6.2 managing credit and credit related accounts or facilities;

9.6.3 recovering debt;

9.6.4 checking details on proposals and claims for all types of insurance; or

9.6.5 checking details of job applicants and employees.

9.7 We and other organisations may access and use from other countries the information recorded by fraud prevention agencies.

### 10\. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

10.1 We reserve the right to change this Policy at any time and any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page.
